Hey Hello Guys Welcome back to my YouTube
channel So Guys today's video is going to be very
informative in that Guys in today's
video I will talk about how I
planned my car's insurance So
Guys what happened last month while
driving I hit a pole due to which the front number of my car
is broken I followed all the tips
given by Justice Yatindra above So its fun to do a
repairing course outside for about ₹5000 If
I had got it repaired by someone then
I thought that I will get the
insurance plan done for the repairing done So Guys
today I am going to talk about how I made
my insurance claim, what is the
procedure for making a claim but
what things you have to keep in mind while landing this year
and I will tell you some such points
which can get
rejected in the fort according to the size So Guys if
you are new to this channel then please subscribe to the channel
and also like my
video So Guys
like this video and keep the time ne
500 tow guide fast  Complete 500 likes
guys it's time for destruction let's
start the video a
that the above is in the well so
let's talk first but due to the reason
which is
your request for car insurance claim then the first
reason is if you do
n't have a valid driving license or you do
n't have the vaccine place and you can do this so whenever
you make an insurance claim guys that
Bigg Boss must be valid so guys
if it has been pointed out that people have purchased their second
hand car the car has been registered in the name of Malwa Shiv
but
as per the program it is not in your name then in this case
also you will not get the mark of claim so guys
whenever you purchase a second hand car then along with the
insurance the condition is
also done in your name guys the third
point is that you know now if you have
CNG or some other mode of fuel in your car
and you do
not tell some companies while taking your insurance after getting this notification then
guys in this case also you may get
rejection in the insurance so whatever it
is  Tell that to any Saurabh company and you will have to pay the
premium for the same year, so guys the points
increase, then
you should not use such a commercial vehicle, if the
car gets into an accident in a Bhramar, then at that
time you will
not get the plane which is available, you will have to do the repairing course
on your website, so
digestive points, if you are
driving the car after drinking alcohol and your Bhagwan Nagar gets
edited, in this pick you will
not get the plane, so guys my
request to you is that never
drive a two wheeler or four wheeler after drinking alcohol, so guys let's
talk to the last point that is inclusion behavior, so guys, suppose
if
you get into an accident tomorrow and the medicines that you get are the same, what happens
when your car reaches the service center
and the engine stops working, then
guys in this case the insurance
company can take action in the insurance fort, so guys the
work of all the cases is inspected, so
always toss the car
I will do it anyway, first of all whenever you open an account
you have to visit Hey Neeraj service center within 24 to 30 hours
and also inform the job source
company, so to
claim insurance you have to
tell a strong story about
how your accident happened, when and at which place
it happened, you had to give that statement to him,
I told my sister that my
car collided with Shiv and when I said
that I put bricks, it was going backwards and
collided with the tow car, today was the story, I
told my saver Ramesh, then he
filled the form, after filling the form
you have to call customer care, you have to
tell them the same information, so
guys one thing to notice is that whichever is
effective drops should have a valid driving license, even
if the driver does not have a
business then your car
insurance claim can be rejected, so
after calling customer care
you must have the intention to stop the test match, you must have
submitted the cadets and skin care, so
guys understand that the reason is that  The service center
people keep it, after that this amount goes to Jyoti
Aunty's place, who installs the cord to see
where the damage is and in many
cases if you keep the damage from both sides
then you will get only one installment, so
guys when you love God you have to spend at
least 12 16130 rupees on the successful incharge,
so after leaving this car in the service center
you have to wait for some time,
whatever the office printer
people will charge you, in how much time will the car get
repaired, so guys after about a
week the zoom right, it is repaired, so
now I am taking my car to the service
center, till then turn on Vivo
[Music] do it
[Praise]
[Music] do it, do it, do it, how to
reduce the tax, repairing course,
term insurance, my elder brother had to arrange for ₹100 more, the
picture of which you were able to
see, so you can see this bill,
subscribe, you do not get it and
subscribe, in today's video I hope
you liked the video  If you liked the video then
please like this video
and subscribe to my channel.